The Nice Guy
الرجل اللطيف
THIS DRAMA SERIES IS FICTIONAL, AND THE PERSONS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
هذه السلسلة الدرامية خيالية، والأشخاص والأماكن والمنظمات،
SETTINGS AND EVENTS DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA SERIES HAVE BEEN FICTIONALLY CREATED
تم إنشاء الإعدادات والأحداث الموضحة في هذه السلسلة الدرامية بشكل خيالي
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED IN SAFE CONDITIONS
تم تصوير الممثلين الأطفال والحيوانات في ظروف آمنة
WITH THE CONSENT OF AND IN THE PRESENCE OF GUARDIANS
بموافقة الأوصياء وبحضورهم
Seokhee!
سيوكي!
Seokkyung!
سيوكيونغ!
- Are you okay? - What? Yes.
- هل أنت بخير؟ - ماذا؟ نعم.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
Okay, let's go.
حسنا، دعنا نذهب.
Come at me. Come on.
تعال إلي. تعال.
You bastard!
أيها الوغد!
- Stop them! - Hey, stop!
- أوقفوهم! - مهلاً، توقفوا!
Seokhee, start the car.
سيوكي، قم بتشغيل السيارة.
Hurry!
عجل!
What the heck? Unlock the door, now!
ماذا بحق الجحيم؟ افتح الباب الآن!
Do it yourself.
افعلها بنفسك.
- Is that the key? - It is.
- هل هذا هو المفتاح؟ - نعم هو كذلك.
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
Hey!
يا!
Come on, boss, stretch your arm further! Darn it.
هيا يا رئيس، مدّ ذراعك أكثر! اللعنة.
Gosh, boss.
يا إلهي، يا رئيس.
Should I report them to the police for kidnapping, battery, and confinement?
هل يجب أن أبلغ عنهم للشرطة بتهمة الاختطاف والضرب والحبس؟
- Do what? Call the cops? - Yes.
- ماذا أفعل؟ أتصل بالشرطة؟ - نعم.
Call the cops? Think before you speak, fool!
اتصل بالشرطة؟ فكّر قبل أن تتكلم يا أحمق!
- I can't reach it. - Stretch, you punk!
- لا أستطيع الوصول إليه. - تمدد، أيها الأحمق!
Are you two all right? Are you hurt?
هل أنتم بخير؟ هل أنتم مصابون؟
The kind of things I get involved in thanks to my genius sister!
هذا هو نوع الأشياء التي أشارك فيها بفضل أختي العبقرية!
Seokkyung, where's your stuff?
سيوكيونج، أين أغراضك؟
He asked you a question.
لقد سألك سؤالا.
In a dorm room.
في غرفة النوم.
A dorm room? That's where you went after you made that mess and left us?
غرفة نوم؟ أين ذهبتِ بعد أن تركتِنا؟
That's okay, I don't need it.
لا بأس، لا أحتاج إليه.
Seokcheol, just drop me off anywhere near the Hangang Bridge.
سوكتشول، فقط أنزلني في أي مكان بالقرب من جسر هانجانج.
- Jeez. - The Hangang Bridge?
- يا إلهي. - جسر هانجانج؟
The thought of getting an earful from me makes you want to jump off a bridge?
هل فكرة أن تسمع مني كلامًا طويلًا تجعلك ترغب في القفز من الجسر؟
Hey, don't talk like that.
مهلا، لا تتحدث بهذه الطريقة.
I'm too ashamed to face you.
أنا أشعر بالخجل الشديد من مواجهتك.
Just drop me off at the Hangang Bridge, Seokcheol.
فقط أنزلني عند جسر هانجانج، سيوكتشول.
What a joke.
يا لها من مزحة!
Jumping into the Hangang River would be a luxury for you.
القفز في نهر هانجانج سيكون بمثابة ترف بالنسبة لك.
From now on, you have no right to say anything or make any decisions.
من الآن فصاعدا، ليس لديك الحق في قول أي شيء أو اتخاذ أي قرار.
Where's that room? Tell us.
أين تلك الغرفة؟ أخبرنا.
Go straight.
انطلق الأمام.
- Open. - Open the door now.
- افتح. - افتح الباب الآن.
Go on.
إستمر.
Come on in.
تفضل بالدخول.
Why do you have all these playing cards? It's like a factory in here.
لماذا لديك كل هذه الأوراق؟ المكان هنا أشبه بمصنع.
Well, I get lonely and frustrated when I'm alone,
حسنًا، أشعر بالوحدة والإحباط عندما أكون وحدي،
so I try to tell my fortune, hoping things will be better tomorrow.
لذلك أحاول أن أتنبأ بمستقبلي، على أمل أن تتحسن الأمور غدًا.
Come on, pack up.
هيا، احزم أمتعتك.
February plum blossom means "lover," right?
زهرة البرقوق في شهر فبراير تعني "الحبيب"، أليس كذلك؟
The September chrysanthemum card means "a drinking guest."
بطاقة الأقحوان لشهر سبتمبر تعني "ضيف الشرب".
Guess that means you'll go drinking.
أعتقد أن هذا يعني أنك ستذهب للشرب.
- Damn it, I hate how accurate it is. - You know quite well.
- اللعنة، أنا أكره مدى دقتها. - أنت تعرف ذلك جيدًا.
I used to watch Mom doing it.
كنت أشاهد أمي تفعل ذلك.
How's Mom?
كيف حال أمي؟
Is she well?
هل هي بخير؟
Forget it. You don't deserve to ask about her.
انسى الأمر، لا تستحق أن تسأل عنها.
She's doing fine.
إنها بخير.
Now stop dillydallying and pack up your things.
الآن توقف عن المماطلة وقم بجمع أغراضك.
What's this T-shirt?
ما هذا القميص؟
- That's Hyeonggeun's. - Why is his T-shirt here?
- هذا قميص هيونغجون. - لماذا قميصه هنا؟
Whenever I miss him or I can't fall asleep,
كلما افتقدته أو لم أستطع النوم،
I cover my face with it and go to sleep.
أغطي وجهي به وأذهب للنوم.
- How dramatic and pitiful. - I'm not.
- كم هو دراماتيكي ومثير للشفقة. - أنا لست كذلك.
When I put the T-shirt over my eyes like this,
عندما أضع القميص على عيني بهذا الشكل،
I can feel Hyeonggeun's essence...
أستطيع أن أشعر بجوهر هيونغجون...
...embrace my whole body, and I can sleep well.
...احتضن جسدي بأكمله، وسأتمكن من النوم جيدًا.
You don't have kids. You won't understand.
ليس لديك أطفال. لن تفهم.
It's drenched in your tears and snot.
إنها غارقة في دموعك ومخاطك.
Anyway, does that make him appear in your dreams?
على أية حال، هل هذا يجعله يظهر في أحلامك؟
He's crazy about playgrounds nowadays. Play with him in your dreams.
إنه مولع بالملاعب هذه الأيام. العب معه في أحلامك.
Mom's knees ache from taking care of him and running around him all day.
ركبتي أمي تؤلمني من العناية به والجري حوله طوال اليوم.
- Did you know that? - Really?
- هل تعلم ذلك؟ - حقا؟
Hyeonggeun must be having fun at the playground.
يبدو أن هيونغجيون يستمتع بوقته في الملعب.
I'm sure he doesn't want to see me. He must hate me.
أنا متأكد أنه لا يريد رؤيتي. لا بد أنه يكرهني.
I'd like to see him in my dreams, but he's never appeared, not once.
أود أن أراه في أحلامي، لكنه لم يظهر أبدًا، ولا مرة واحدة.
Then why do something that would make him hate you?
إذن لماذا تفعل شيئًا يجعله يكرهك؟
Stop already. I know what I did, and I know it's all my fault.
توقف الآن. أنا أعلم ما فعلته، وأعلم أن كل هذا خطئي.
But...
لكن...
...I miss my Hyeonggeun so much.
...أفتقد هيونغجون كثيرًا.
I can't help myself. I want to hug him each night.
لا أستطيع منع نفسي. أريد أن أعانقه كل ليلة.
Hyeonggeun.
هيونغجون.
Park Seokkyung, my older sister,
بارك سوك كيونغ، أختي الكبرى،
who was as much of a troublemaker as I was, if not more.
الذي كان مثيرًا للمشاكل مثلي، إن لم يكن أكثر.
HAIR SALON
صالون شعر
I left the stove on.
تركت الموقد مشتعلا.
- You need to be back in 10 minutes. - Okay.
- يجب عليك العودة خلال 10 دقائق. - حسنًا.
I got it!
حصلت عليه!
My sister used to work as a hairdresser.
كانت أختي تعمل مصففة شعر.
She got pregnant and had a shotgun wedding.
لقد حملت وأقامت حفل زفافها.
Right after a year of a happy honeymoon...
بعد مرور عام كامل على شهر العسل السعيد...
MYOUNGSAN DISTRICT COURT
محكمة مقاطعة ميونغسان
...she got divorced.
...لقد تم الطلاق منها.
The reason for the divorce was my sister's domestic abuse
وكان سبب الطلاق هو العنف الأسري الذي مارسته أختي
that was fueled by her husband's affair.
والتي كانت بسبب علاقة زوجها.
- God, seriously... - Bye.
- يا إلهي، بجد... - مع السلامة.
Instead of getting alimony,
بدلا من الحصول على النفقة،
she had to compensate him for his broken nose.
كان عليها أن تعوضه عن أنفه المكسور.
She took up gambling
لقد بدأت القمار
in an attempt to fill the void that her failed marriage created.
في محاولة لملء الفراغ الذي خلفه زواجها الفاشل.
Let's see.
دعونا نرى.
She secretly coaxed Mom and lost our house deed to the bank.
لقد أقنعت أمي سراً وخسرت سند ملكية منزلنا لصالح البنك.
Seokkyung was the first to run away when we got beaten up as kids.
كان سيوكيونج هو أول من هرب عندما تعرضنا للضرب عندما كنا أطفالاً.
Before Father could break her legs for what she had done,
قبل أن يتمكن الأب من كسر ساقيها بسبب ما فعلته،
she chose to flee in the middle of the night.
اختارت الفرار في منتصف الليل.
Her phone was out of service, and her address unknown.
وكان هاتفها خارج الخدمة، وعنوانها غير معروف.
We heard rumors of her being spotted at different gambling dens around town.
سمعنا شائعات حول رؤيتها في العديد من نوادي القمار في جميع أنحاء المدينة.
On the way back home with her,
في طريق العودة إلى المنزل معها،
the three of us were quiet, lost in our own thoughts.
كنا الثلاثة في صمت، غارقين في أفكارنا الخاصة.
Come on.
تعال.
It hurts.
إنه يؤلمني.
Here. Take this in.
هنا. خذ هذا.
Sorry about the trouble I caused you guys today.
آسف على الإزعاج الذي سببته لكم اليوم.
As long as you're aware of it.
طالما أنك على علم بذلك.
Listen to what Seokhee says, and stay put in this house.
استمع إلى ما يقوله سيوكي، وابق في هذا المنزل.
Seokcheol, I could just go to another dorm room--
سوكتشول، يمكنني الذهاب إلى غرفة نوم أخرى--
No, you won't.
لا، لن تفعل ذلك.
Go on. And don't you dare step out of the house.
إستمر. ولا تجرؤ على الخروج من المنزل.
Hurry up.
اسرع.
- Seokcheol, I'm scared-- - Just go in already.
- سوكتشول، أنا خائف-- - فقط اذهب إلى الداخل.
You better not run away again.
من الأفضل أن لا تهرب مرة أخرى.
The Nice Guy
الرجل اللطيف
- Gosh. I'll do it. Go and rest.
يا إلهي، سأفعلها. اذهب واسترح.
You're so young, and you've been working so hard this early in the morning.
أنت صغير جدًا، وقد كنت تعمل بجد في هذا الوقت المبكر من الصباح.
You said so yourself.
لقد قلت ذلك بنفسك.
If I don't want to suffer later, I should try and earn more now.
إذا كنت لا أريد أن أعاني لاحقًا، فيجب أن أحاول كسب المزيد الآن.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Work hard.
اعمل بجد.
MIYOUNG
مي يونغ
Good morning. Let's work hard today too.
صباح الخير. لنعمل بجد اليوم أيضًا.
Sure. Let's work hard.
بالتأكيد. دعونا نعمل بجد.
Yes, sir. I'll work hard.
نعم سيدي، سأعمل بجد.
You're eating well.
أنت تأكل جيدا.
- Good morning, Uncle. - Hey. How did you sleep?
- صباح الخير يا عمي. - أهلًا، كيف نمت؟
Sit down. I'll reheat the soup.
اجلس، سأعيد تسخين الحساء.
Your mom would also use two sheets of seaweed to wrap the rice.
ستستخدم والدتك أيضًا ورقتين من الأعشاب البحرية لتغليف الأرز.
Do you miss her?
هل تفتقدها؟
Yes.
نعم.
Wait a bit longer. I'll bring your mom home.
انتظر قليلًا، سأحضر أمك إلى المنزل.
- Really? - Yes.
- حقا؟ - نعم.
But make sure you keep this a secret from Grandma and Grandpa, okay?
ولكن تأكد من إبقاء هذا الأمر سرًا عن جدك وجدك، حسنًا؟
Okay.
تمام.
Shake on it?
رجّ عليه؟
Promise.
يعد.
Wake up.
استيقظ.
How long are you going to sleep? Wake up.
كم من الوقت ستنام؟ استيقظ.
I'm not used to waking up this early.
أنا لست معتادًا على الاستيقاظ مبكرًا.
What a joke.
يا لها من مزحة!
It's cold and windy here.
إنه بارد وعاصف هنا.
- Get up! - Come on!
-انهض! - هيا!
- Time for breakfast. - Breakfast?
- وقت الإفطار. - الإفطار؟
A sinner should eat too.
وينبغي للخاطئ أن يأكل أيضاً.
It's too sweet.
ًانها حلوة جدا.
You ordered these in, didn't you?
لقد طلبت هذه، أليس كذلك؟
I won't take your complaints about food. Don't piss me off.
لن أقبل شكواك بشأن الطعام. لا تغضبني.
I never complain about food.
أنا لا أشتكي من الطعام أبدًا.
But this much sugar in your food is bad for you.
لكن هذه الكمية الكبيرة من السكر في طعامك سيئة بالنسبة لك.
If you keep this up, I'll call Father and tell him you're here.
إذا واصلت على هذا المنوال، سأتصل بأبي وأخبره أنك هنا.
You get meaner by the day.
تصبح أكثر قسوة يوما بعد يوم.
When will you go back home?
متى ستعود إلى المنزل؟
Hyeonggeun's school has invited parents to sit in on classes.
دعت مدرسة هيونغجون أولياء الأمور لحضور الفصول الدراسية.
Other kids' parents are gonna be there.
سيكون آباء الأطفال الآخرين هناك.
Are you going to make Hyeonggeun go with his grandma?
هل ستجعل هيونغجون يذهب مع جدته؟
He's gonna look like an orphan.
إنه سيبدو مثل اليتيم.
Stop tearing up, and say something.
توقف عن البكاء وقل شيئا.
You must have a plan.
يجب أن يكون لديك خطة.
I want to go home too.
أريد أن أذهب إلى المنزل أيضاً.
I want to hold Hyeonggeun's hand and take him to school.
أريد أن أمسك يد هيونغجون وأخذه إلى المدرسة.
But I'm too scared of Father to go back.
لكنني خائفة جدًا من والدي ولا أستطيع العودة.
He might really break my legs.
ربما يكسر ساقي حقا.
Isn't that a small price to pay in exchange for being with your son?
أليس هذا ثمنًا صغيرًا تدفعه مقابل البقاء مع ابنك؟
Seokkyung,
سيوكيونغ،
did you know I left home because I got sick of sharing my room with you?
هل تعلم أنني غادرت المنزل لأنني سئمت من مشاركة غرفتي معك؟
Why are you wearing those socks?
لماذا ترتدي هذه الجوارب؟
I was cold.
لقد كنت باردًا.
Do I need your permission for this too?
هل أحتاج إلى إذنك لهذا أيضًا؟
Take them off. They're my favorite pair.
انزعهم. إنهم زوجي المفضل.
Kihong bought them for me.
لقد اشتراها لي كيهونغ.
Oh, no, you must be upset.
أوه، لا، لا بد أنك منزعج.
Fine, I'll take them off. Sheesh.
حسنًا، سأزيلهم. يا إلهي.
There.
هناك.
- Happy now? - Yes, I'm happy.
- سعيدة الآن؟ - نعم، أنا سعيدة.
Only one sheet of seaweed from now on.
ورقة واحدة فقط من الأعشاب البحرية من الآن فصاعدا.
Why do you always take two?
لماذا تأخذ دائما اثنين؟
Put one of them here.
ضع واحدا منهم هنا.
God, you're being so petty.
يا إلهي، أنت تافه جدًا.
SIS FROM HOUSE
أخت من المنزل
- She keeps calling. - "House"?
- إنها تستمر في الاتصال. - "البيت"؟
Don't pick up. You ignored all my calls, after all.
لا ترد. لقد تجاهلت جميع مكالماتي، على أي حال.
- I'll answer it. - I said don't!
- سأجيب عليه. - قلت لا تفعل!
- Hello. - Seokkyung.
- مرحباً. - سيوكيونغ.
- Where did you run off with my money? - Oh, well...
- أين هربت بأموالي؟ - أوه، حسنًا...
Do you think you can hide from me, you witch?
هل تعتقدين أنك تستطيعين الاختباء مني أيتها الساحرة؟
You sound very angry.
يبدو أنك غاضب جدًا.
When I find you, I'm gonna shred you into tiny pieces.
عندما أجدك، سأقطعك إلى قطع صغيرة.
- You'll do what? - Hey!
- ماذا ستفعل؟ - هي!
- Who are you? - Her sister.
- من أنت؟ - أختها.
- You got a problem? - What?
- هل لديك مشكلة؟ - ماذا؟
Firstly, you don't need to repay a gambling debt.
أولاً، ليس عليك سداد دين القمار.
And the guy who followed her around is a detective.
والرجل الذي يتبعها هو المحقق.
If you lay a hand on my sister, I'm sure they'll put you behind bars.
إذا وضعت يدك على أختي، فأنا متأكد من أنهم سيضعونك خلف القضبان.
Do you take me for a fool?
هل تظنني أحمق؟
- Get lost! - You witch.
- إذهبي إلى الخارج! - أيتها الساحرة.
- You disgusting piece of-- - Go and off yourself, bitch.
- يا قطعة مقززة من-- - اذهبي وابتعدي عن نفسك، أيتها العاهرة.
Don't talk down to me. You don't even know me.
لا تتحدث معي باستخفاف. أنت لا تعرفني حتى.
Don't you dare call again.
لا تجرؤ على الاتصال مرة أخرى.
- I'll kill you. - You stupid little--
- سأقتلك. - أيها الطفل الغبي الصغير--
She's ridiculous.
إنها سخيفة.
She better not show up again, or I'll headbutt her.
من الأفضل لها أن لا تظهر مرة أخرى، وإلا سأضربها برأسي.
Hey. Do you think headbutting someone is easy?
مهلا، هل تعتقد أن ضرب شخص ما برأسه أمر سهل؟
You need the skills for it.
تحتاج إلى المهارات اللازمة لذلك.
What kind of skills do you need? All you do is butt them.
ما نوع المهارات التي تحتاجها؟ كل ما عليك فعله هو مواجهتها.
It's not just about butting into their forehead.
لا يتعلق الأمر فقط بالاصطدام بجباههم.
You need to have a hard forehead
يجب أن يكون لديك جبهة صلبة
so your opponent gets hurt when you butt them, but you don't.
لذلك فإن خصمك يتعرض للأذى عندما تضربه، ولكنك لا تتعرض للأذى.
Go on. Feel my forehead.
إستمر. أشعر بجبهتي.
My goodness.
يا إلهي.
It's so hard.
إنه صعب للغاية.
- Isn't it? - Yes.
- أليس كذلك؟ - نعم.
It's something you're born with.
إنه شيء تولد به.
- Basketball players must be tall. - Yes.
- يجب أن يكون لاعبو كرة السلة طويلين. - نعم.
- Soccer players must be fast.
- يجب أن يكون لاعبو كرة القدم سريعين.
Headbutters have a hard forehead. Bam!
جباههم صلبة. بام!
Really?
حقًا؟
- You think I could do it? - Let me check.
- هل تعتقد أنني أستطيع فعل ذلك؟ - دعني أتحقق.
What? What is it?
ماذا؟ ما هو؟
Hey. You could do it.
مهلا، يمكنك فعل ذلك.
- Really? - Yes.
- حقا؟ - نعم.
Is my forehead hard enough?
هل جبهتي صلبة بما فيه الكفاية؟
Let me feel it. My gosh.
دعني أشعر به. يا إلهي.
Geummyeong Bank. The branch manager is Moon Gisu.
بنك غيوميونغ. مدير الفرع هو مون غيسو.
Yes. You'd better not make a mistake.
نعم، من الأفضل ألا ترتكب خطأً.
If you do, I'll kill you.
إذا فعلت ذلك، سأقتلك.
Okay. I trust you.
حسنًا، أنا أثق بك.
I'm hanging up. Bye.
سأغلق الخط. مع السلامة.
- Boss. - Yes.
- رئيس. - نعم.
Jindeuk said he'll get an appointment in two days.
قال جيندوك أنه سيحصل على موعد خلال يومين.
The branch manager bends to his every whim.
مدير الفرع ينحني لكل نزوة.
Okay, good job.
حسنًا، عمل جيد.
That girl Seokkyung is just like you. She's so reckless.
تلك الفتاة سوك كيونغ مثلك تمامًا، متهورة جدًا.
She is your daughter, after all.
إنها ابنتك، بعد كل شيء.
She causes trouble as much as you do.
إنها تسبب المشاكل مثلما تفعل أنت.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Did I say something wrong?
هل قلت شيئا خاطئا؟
Would you look at the time. I should get going.
هل يمكنك أن تنظر إلى الساعة؟ يجب أن أذهب.
- Get out of here! - Bye.
- اخرج من هنا! - وداعا.
Punk.
فاسق.
This is District Three.
هذه هي المنطقة الثالثة.
It's the prime location of Myoungsan City's redevelopment area.
إنه الموقع الرئيسي لمنطقة إعادة تطوير مدينة ميونغسان.
As long as we secure this area,
طالما أننا نؤمن هذه المنطقة،
we can easily get our hands on future development areas. Understood?
يمكننا بسهولة تحديد مجالات التطوير المستقبلية. هل فهمت؟
Yes, sir!
نعم سيدي!
The problem is the tenants again.
المشكلة هي المستأجرين مرة أخرى.
The developer promised compensation and negotiations,
ووعد المطور بالتعويض والمفاوضات،
but they're unhappy, and getting in the way of the demolition.
لكنهم غير سعداء، ويقفون في طريق الهدم.
There's one particularly reckless jerk.
هناك أحمق متهور بشكل خاص.
Show us his picture.
أرنا صورته.
That's the President of the Tenant Housing Committee,
هذا هو رئيس لجنة سكن المستأجرين،
Kim Jinho.
كيم جينهو.
If we can take him down, District Three will be ours in no time.
إذا تمكنا من القضاء عليه، فإن المنطقة الثالثة ستكون بين أيدينا في أي وقت من الأوقات.
- Got it? - Yes, sir!
- فهمت؟ - نعم سيدي!
Take a good look at him. Remember his face.
أنظر إليه جيدًا. تذكر وجهه.
Tenants still live here! Provide relocation measures!
لا يزال المستأجرون يعيشون هنا! قدّموا لنا إجراءات نقل!
Forced demolition is unacceptable,
الهدم القسري أمر غير مقبول.
Oseon E&C!
أوسيون إي آند سي!
Forced demolition is unacceptable!
الهدم القسري أمر غير مقبول!
Forced demolition is unacceptable!
الهدم القسري أمر غير مقبول!
TENANTS DID NOT CONSENT
المستأجرون لم يوافقوا
We fight together!
نحن نقاتل معا!
Hey.
يا.
I'll go in first. You guys wait here.
سأدخل أولاً. انتظروا هنا.
- Let me come with you. - You're the last person I want with me.
- دعني أذهب معك. - أنت آخر شخص أريده معي.
Don't make things worse. Stay out of sight, got it?
لا تُفاقم الأمور. ابقَ بعيدًا عن الأنظار، فهمت؟
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I'm a contract employee. I work for the developer.
أنا موظف بعقد. أعمل لدى المطور.
- Park Seokcheol, Myoungsan Industries. - Give me your ID.
- بارك سوكتشول، صناعات ميونغسان. - أعطني هويتك.
- Sign here. - Okay.
-وقع هنا. -حسنا.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Come on.
تعال.
You said you were gonna quit. What are you doing here?
قلتَ إنك ستستقيل. ماذا تفعل هنا؟
It's my last gig. Give me that.
هذه آخر حفلة لي. أعطني إياها.
Don't you trust me?
ألا تثق بي؟
If I say it's my last gig, it is.
إذا قلت أن هذه هي حفلتي الأخيرة، فهي كذلك.
Don't worry, I'm better at this than you are.
لا تقلق، أنا أفضل منك في هذا.
Call the Tenant Housing Committee.
اتصل بلجنة سكن المستأجرين.
Tell them someone's coming up.
أخبرهم أن شخصًا ما قادم.
It won't be easy.
لن يكون الأمر سهلا.
The committee president is the nastiest person you'll meet.
رئيس اللجنة هو الشخص الأكثر سوءًا الذي ستقابله.
It'll be a disaster.
ستكون كارثة.
I think so too.
أعتقد ذلك أيضًا.
But, sir, I heard that the team leader of District Three is Park Seokcheol.
لكن سيدي، سمعت أن قائد فريق المنطقة الثالثة هو بارك سوكتشول.
Wow.
رائع.
What would Kim Changsoo have done without Seokcheol?
ماذا كان كيم تشانغسو سيفعل بدون سوكتشول؟
But even Seokcheol won't be able to pull this off.
ولكن حتى سوكتشول لن يكون قادرًا على القيام بذلك.
That's why I gave up on the bidding.
لهذا السبب تخليت عن المزايدة.
FIGHT TOGETHER
نقاتل معًا
What could you possibly want to talk to me about?
ما الذي قد ترغب في التحدث معي عنه؟
President, the longer you resist, the longer you suffer.
السيد الرئيس، كلما طال صمودك، كلما طال عانيت.
You know that very well.
أنت تعرف ذلك جيدا.
The developer wants us to barge right in today,
يريد المطور منا أن نتدخل اليوم،
but I have no intention of doing that.
ولكن ليس لدي أي نية للقيام بذلك.
Let's talk it out.
دعونا نتحدث عن ذلك.
There's no need to fight and shed blood.
ليست هناك حاجة للقتال وسفك الدماء.
It seems like thugs these days are getting more subtle with their threats.
يبدو أن البلطجية هذه الأيام أصبحوا أكثر دهاءً في تهديداتهم.
It's not a threat.
إنه ليس تهديدا.
I'm asking for a negotiation.
أطلب التفاوض.
I know thugs like you very well.
أنا أعرف البلطجية مثلك جيدًا.
Poor jerks.
مساكين الأغبياء.
You act all tough, but you're actually the most pitiful creatures.
تتصرف كشخص قوي، لكنك في الواقع أكثر المخلوقات إثارة للشفقة.
Have you seen anyone prepared to die for a cause?
هل رأيت أحدا مستعدا للموت من أجل قضية ما؟
Don't think of negotiating with me.
لا تفكر بالتفاوض معي.
Now leave.
إذهب الآن.
HOUSING COMMITTEE
لجنة الإسكان
- Thank you. - Sure.
- شكرا لك. - بالتأكيد.
- Boss.
- رئيس.
Let's go eat.
دعنا نذهب لتناول الطعام.
- I'm good. You guys go ahead. - Okay.
- أنا بخير. تفضلوا. - حسنًا.
- Dusik. - Yes, sir.
- دوسيك. - نعم سيدي.
I need a word with you.
أحتاج إلى كلمة معك.
- You guys go on. - We'll get going.
- استمروا يا رفاق. - سوف ننطلق.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
After lunch, go back to District Three.
بعد الغداء، العودة إلى المنطقة الثالثة.
Again?
مرة أخرى؟
Go find out if there's a cop or someone who messes with the tenants.
اذهب واكتشف ما إذا كان هناك شرطي أو شخص يتلاعب بالمستأجرين.
And the President is a tough guy, so be careful.
والرئيس رجل قوي، لذا كن حذرا.
I understand.
أفهم.
- Call me if anything happens. - Okay.
- اتصل بي إذا حدث أي شيء. - حسنًا.
- Go. You must be hungry. - Yes, sir.
- اذهب. لا بد أنك جائع. - نعم سيدي.
- Have a good lunch, sir. - Okay. Bye.
- غداء هنيئًا يا سيدي. - حسنًا. مع السلامة.
Seokcheol is the team lead, right?
سوكتشول هو قائد الفريق، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Let's use this chance
دعونا نستخدم هذه الفرصة
to get rid of Kang Taehoon's lackeys.
للتخلص من أتباع كانغ تايهون.
We can't afford to share any land in this small country.
لا يمكننا تحمل مشاركة أي أرض في هذا البلد الصغير.
If they won't reason with us,
إذا لم يجادلونا،
get the contractors to wipe them out.
اطلب من المقاولين القضاء عليهم.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
SEOKHEE
سيوكي
Gosh, hold on.
يا إلهي، انتظر.
Wait, wait...
انتظر، انتظر...
- Hello? - Why are you panting?
- مرحبا؟ - لماذا تلهث؟
I rushed to answer your call, and I fell down.
لقد هرعت للرد على ندائك، فسقطت.
- Why did you fall? - It was slippery.
- لماذا سقطت؟ - كان زلقًا.
Don't take so long to answer my calls. It makes me anxious.
لا تتأخر في الرد على مكالماتي، فهذا يُقلقني.
I was in the toilet.
كنت في المرحاض.
Take your phone to the toilet.
خذ هاتفك إلى المرحاض.
And don't answer any calls from the house.
ولا تجيب على أي مكالمات من المنزل.
Got it.
فهمتها.
Don't run away.
لا تهرب.
Listen, I have nowhere left to run to.
اسمع، ليس لدي مكان آخر لأهرب إليه.
Stop doubting me.
توقف عن الشك بي.
You've given me no reason to stop.
لم تعطوني أي سبب للتوقف.
Just stay holed up in the house.
فقط ابقى محصورا في المنزل.
Fine.
بخير.
Not going to eat?
لن تأكل؟
Ah. No. Someone I know is visiting. I'm giving her a consultation.
آه. لا، شخص أعرفه يزورني. سأقدم لها استشارة.
Oh. Shall I go get you a sandwich then?
أوه، هل أذهب لأحضر لك شطيرة إذن؟
No, that's okay.
لا، لا بأس بذلك.
So, what happened to Seokkyung? Did she go back home?
إذًا، ماذا حدث لسوكيونغ؟ هل عادت إلى المنزل؟
She's staying with me.
إنها ستبقى معي.
- What about your parents? - She's too scared of Father to go back.
- ماذا عن والديك؟ - إنها خائفة جدًا من والدها ولا تستطيع العودة.
I can't kick her out, either.
لا أستطيع أن أطردها أيضًا.
That's true. Your father might actually break her legs.
هذا صحيح. قد يكسر والدك ساقيها.
But if she's with you, I can't come over to your place.
لكن إذا كانت معك، لا أستطيع أن آتي إلى منزلك.
You won't have to wait long. I'll send her back home as soon as I can.
لن تنتظر طويلاً. سأعيدها إلى المنزل بأسرع ما يمكن.
If she refuses to go, I'll drag her back home myself.
إذا رفضت الذهاب، سأعيدها إلى المنزل بنفسي.
All right.
حسنًا.
- You got this. - Thanks.
- لقد حصلت على هذا. - شكرا لك.
Enjoy your meal.
أتمنى لك وجبة شهية.
- Dr. Jang! - Oh, yes, madam.
- دكتور جانج! - أوه نعم سيدتي.
I think I'm a little early for my appointment.
أعتقد أنني وصلت مبكرًا بعض الشيء إلى موعدي.
Goodness, it's so hard to get ahold of you.
يا إلهي، من الصعب جدًا الوصول إليك.
My husband said you get the most appointments in our hospital.
قال زوجي أنك تحصلين على معظم المواعيد في مستشفانا.
- Did the director say really that? - Yes.
- هل قال المخرج ذلك حقًا؟ - نعم.
My husband praises you all the time.
زوجي يمدحك طوال الوقت.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
How is your back?
كيف ظهرك؟
That was an excuse.
لقد كان هذا عذرا.
I came here to introduce you to someone.
لقد جئت إلى هنا لأقدم لك شخصًا ما.
Jinhee.
جينهي.
Why don't you come in? Come on in.
لماذا لا تدخل؟ تفضل بالدخول.
This is Jinhee, my daughter.
هذه جينهي، ابنتي.
You've heard, right? She's studying in the States.
سمعتوا، صح؟ هي تدرس في أمريكا.
She flew in for her vacation.
لقد سافرت جواً لقضاء إجازتها.
She's a big fan of yours, Dr. Jang.
إنها من أكبر معجبيك، دكتور جانج.
She says you're the most handsome and gentle doctor here.
تقول أنك الطبيب الأكثر وسامة ولطفًا هنا.
- Hello.
- مرحبا.
I'm sorry, I should've asked you this before.
أنا آسف، كان ينبغي لي أن أسألك هذا من قبل.
Dr. Jang, do you have a girlfriend?
الدكتور جانج هل لديك صديقة؟
Do you?
هل أنت؟
Uh...
أوه...
Yes, well...
نعم حسنا...
- I don't. - I'm so glad!
- لا أفعل. - أنا سعيد جدًا!
So, I have tickets to a piano concert.
إذن، لدي تذاكر لحفلة البيانو.
Would you like to go with Jinhee?
هل ترغب بالذهاب مع جينهي؟
- Do you like piano music? - Piano...
- هل تحب موسيقى البيانو؟ - بيانو...
Yes, well...
نعم حسنا...
- Ms. Seokhee. - Yes?
- السيدة سيوكيهي. - نعم؟
Since this is not a consultation,
وبما أن هذه ليست استشارة،
you can leave.
يمكنك المغادرة.
Oh.
أوه.
Goodness, you look good together already!
يا إلهي، تبدوان جيدين معًا بالفعل!
My gosh.
يا إلهي.
- Have you had lunch? - No, not yet.
- هل تناولت الغداء؟ - لا، ليس بعد.
- Here are your side dishes. - Thanks.
- ها هي أطباقك الجانبية. - شكرا.
Water, please!
ماء، من فضل!
- Enjoy. - Can I have a bottle of soju?
- استمتع. - هل يمكنني الحصول على زجاجة من السوجو؟
One bottle of soju, coming up!
زجاجة واحدة من السوجو، قادمة!
- Yes? - We'd like a bottle of soju too.
- نعم؟ - نود الحصول على زجاجة من السوجو أيضًا.
Good going today. You worked so hard.
أحسنت اليوم. لقد عملت بجد.
I'm just doing my job.
أنا فقط أقوم بعملي.
PUREUM NURSING HOME YOON HYESOOK'S GUARDIAN
دار رعاية المسنين بوريوم، حارس يون هيسوك
THE CARE EXPENSES ARE PAST DUE PLEASE MAKE YOUR PAYMENT
لقد تأخرت مصاريف الرعاية، يرجى إجراء الدفعة الخاصة بك
Life...
حياة...
albaWorld MEDIA, CONCERTS
ألبا وورلد ميديا، حفلات موسيقية
JAZZ BAR NILBANA
جاز بار نيلبانا
DARE TO BE A STAR
تجرأ على أن تكون نجمًا
Actually, I wanted to give it all up.
في الواقع، كنت أريد أن أتخلى عن كل شيء.
I wanted to sing in front of others, but I couldn't.
أردت أن أغني أمام الآخرين، لكنني لم أستطع.
But I couldn't just give up on my dreams.
ولكنني لم أستطع أن أتخلى عن أحلامي.
Because if I do, there's nothing else left for me.
لأنه إذا فعلت ذلك، فلن يتبقى لي أي شيء آخر.
You have a pretty face.
لديك وجه جميل.
You're good enough.
أنت جيد بما فيه الكفاية.
You're good enough the way you are.
أنت جيد بما فيه الكفاية كما أنت.
Whatever you want to do.
كل ما تريد فعله.
Just remember today.
فقط تذكر اليوم.
You'll do fine wherever you go.
سوف تكون بخير أينما ذهبت.
WE'RE FOR IT! PRO-REDEVELOPMENT COMMITTEE
نحن معها! لجنة إعادة التنمية
Boss, it's a mess here.
يا رئيس، الأمر فوضوي هنا.
Sangyeol and the contractors are dragging the tenants out.
سانجيول والمقاولون يسحبون المستأجرين للخارج.
Come quickly.
تعال بسرعة.
No!
لا!
Let me cover it!
دعني اغطيها!
Hey, what's happening?
مهلا، ماذا يحدث؟
Don't do it.
لا تفعل ذلك.
Shit!
اللعنة!
- Who are you? - Let me go!
- من أنت؟ - دعني أذهب!
Hey, Seokcheol!
مهلا، سوكتشول!
Tenants have the right to oppose!
للمستأجرين الحق في الاعتراض!
I told you to wait.
لقد قلت لك أن تنتظر.
Boss, you should have left this to me.
يا رئيس، كان ينبغي عليك أن تترك هذا الأمر لي.
Now isn't a good time.
الآن ليس الوقت المناسب .
It was the Chairman's orders.
لقد كانت أوامر الرئيس.
What can we do but follow orders from our higher-ups?
ماذا يمكننا أن نفعل سوى اتباع الأوامر الصادرة من رؤسائنا؟
You'll ruin everything at this rate!
سوف تدمر كل شيء بهذا المعدل!
Why are you yelling at me?
لماذا تصرخ علي؟
Take it up the Chairman.
خذها يا رئيس.
I have no say in this.
ليس لي رأي في هذا.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
It's gasoline!
إنه البنزين!
Come on down! Come back here!
انزل! عد إلى هنا!
You bastards!
أيها الأوغاد!
Watch closely.
شاهد عن كثب.
I'm all set.
أنا مستعد تماما.
Come on. Come and get me, bastards!
هيا، تعالوا وخذوني أيها الأوغاد!
Dad!
أب!
- Dad! Dad! - No!
- أبي! أبي! - لا!
You can't go up there!
لا يمكنك الصعود إلى هناك!
Dad, Dad!
أبي، أبي!
Dad!
أب!
Dad...
أب...
Dad.
أب.
Stop your forceful demolition!
اوقفوا هدمكم بالقوة!
Thug contractors, step back!
أيها المقاولون البلطجية، تراجعوا إلى الوراء!
Dad!
أب!
Dad...
أب...
- Dusik. - Yes, sir.
- دوسيك. - نعم سيدي.
Didn't you serve a prison sentence for picking locks?
ألم تقضي عقوبة السجن بسبب فتح الأقفال؟
Yes. It's my specialty.
نعم ، إنه تخصصي.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Come on.
تعال.
You think you can get it done tonight?
هل تعتقد أنك قادر على إنجاز ذلك الليلة؟
I'm doing my best, sir.
أنا أبذل قصارى جهدي، سيدي.
Don't scold him when he's working. You'll distract him.
لا تُوبِّخه أثناء عمله، فهذا يُشتِّت انتباهه.
You keep your mouth shut.
أبقي فمك مغلقا.
- I did it, sir. - What?
- لقد فعلتها يا سيدي. - ماذا؟
Good job, Dusik.
عمل جيد، دوسيك.
Boss. What are you gonna do?
يا رئيس، ماذا ستفعل؟
What else? I'll go in and get him out.
ماذا أيضًا؟ سأدخل وأخرجه.
- You guys wait here. - Yes, sir.
- انتظروا هنا يا رفاق. - نعم سيدي.
Be careful, sir.
كن حذرا يا سيدي.
You shouldn't drink on an empty stomach. It's bad for you.
لا يجب عليك الشرب على معدة فارغة، فهذا مضر.
What did you do? How did you get in?
ماذا فعلت؟ كيف دخلت؟
Well, you know...
حسنا، أنت تعرف...
I walked up the stairs.
صعدت الدرج.
Oh, gosh.
يا إلهي.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
You're making this so hard for me.
أنت تجعل هذا الأمر صعبًا جدًا بالنسبة لي.
I should've quit this job long ago.
كان ينبغي لي أن أترك هذه الوظيفة منذ زمن طويل.
Listen, sir.
إستمع يا سيدي.
Don't waste your precious life here.
لا تضيع حياتك الثمينة هنا.
Let's get out of here.
دعونا نخرج من هنا.
Don't act as if you're trying to save me.
لا تتصرف وكأنك تحاول إنقاذي.
You're nothing but a thug.
أنت لست سوى بلطجي.
I didn't come here to save you.
لم آتي إلى هنا لإنقاذك.
I want to quit my job as a thug.
أريد أن أترك وظيفتي كبلطجي.
But I can't do that if you die in here.
ولكن لا يمكنني أن أفعل ذلك إذا مت هنا.
Not only will I not be able to quit,
لن أكون قادرًا على الإقلاع فحسب،
but my life will get messier than it already is.
لكن حياتي ستصبح أكثر فوضوية مما هي عليه بالفعل.
So, let's just go, okay?
حسنًا، دعنا نذهب، حسنًا؟
What if I don't?
ماذا لو لم أفعل ذلك؟
Then I'll have to use force.
ثم سأضطر إلى استخدام القوة.
Spoken like a true thug.
تحدث مثل البلطجي الحقيقي.
Have you heard of Yeonsinnae's Eyeball?
هل سمعت عن عين يونسيناي؟
Back in my prime, no one pissed me off and walked away unscathed.
في أيام مجدي، لم يزعجني أحد وخرجت سالمًا.
Bring it on.
اجلبه.
Let's see how strong thugs are nowadays.
دعونا نرى مدى قوة البلطجية في أيامنا هذه.
You sure can throw a good punch.
بالتأكيد يمكنك توجيه لكمة جيدة.
All thanks to my good upbringing.
كل الشكر لتربيتي الجيدة.
- Let go! - Please, stop!
-اتركه! -من فضلك، توقف!
Seokcheol went in there?
هل ذهب سوكتشول إلى هناك؟
Yes, well... He said he'd bring the president out.
نعم، حسنًا... لقد قال أنه سيحضر الرئيس.
Okay.
تمام.
Okay, my foot!
حسنا، قدمي!
Will you take responsibility if something happens to Seokcheol, huh?
هل ستتحمل المسؤولية إذا حدث شيء لسيوكتشول، هاه؟
You're scaring me. What's the problem?
أنت تخيفني. ما المشكلة؟
You have no loyalty at all.
ليس لديك أي ولاء على الإطلاق.
Look at what happened.
انظر ماذا حدث
Please stop. I'm exhausted too.
من فضلك توقف، أنا مرهق أيضًا.
Let's end this here.
دعونا ننهي هذا هنا.
Remember I asked you...
تذكر أنني سألتك...
if you'd seen anyone prepared to die.
إذا رأيت أي شخص مستعد للموت.
So...
لذا...
Do you think I'll burn this place up or not?
هل تعتقد أنني سأحرق هذا المكان أم لا؟
Do you know how the homeless suffer?
هل تعلم كيف يعاني المشردون؟
Whether in here or on the streets,
سواء هنا أو في الشوارع،
I'm gonna die either way.
سأموت على أية حال.
Come on, we really need to leave.
هيا، نحن بحاجة حقا إلى المغادرة.
Go!
يذهب!
What's that smoke?
ما هذا الدخان؟
Fire! Fire!
نار! نار!
Call 911!
اتصل بالرقم 911!
Go. It's over anyway.
إذهب، لقد إنتهى الأمر على أية حال.
You shouldn't die too.
لا ينبغي أن تموت أيضاً.
Get out of here.
اخرج من هنا.
Seokcheol!
سوكتشول!
Seokcheol... Seokcheol!
سوكتشول... سوكتشول!
- Park Seokcheol! - No, no!
- بارك سوكتشول! - لا، لا!
- Let go! - Seokcheol!
- دعه يذهب! - سوكتشول!
What about your daughter? What about her?
ماذا عن ابنتك؟ ماذا عنها؟
Get up. Come on.
انهض. هيا.
Get up!
استيقظ!
Seokcheol!
سوكتشول!
Come on! This way!
تعال! من هنا!
- There they are! - They're out!
- ها هم هناك! - لقد خرجوا!
Call an ambulance!
اتصل بالإسعاف!
Boss!
رئيس!
- Are you okay? - Boss!
- هل أنت بخير؟ - رئيس!
- Damn it!
- اللعنة!
Father,
أب،
your grandson Seokcheol's face was printed on the front page of the newspaper.
لقد تم طباعة وجه حفيدك سوكتشول على الصفحة الأولى من الصحيفة.
And it wasn't because he hit someone in the face, like I did.
ولم يكن ذلك لأنه ضرب شخصًا في وجهه، كما فعلت.
He's in the papers because he saved a life.
لقد ظهر في الصحف لأنه أنقذ حياة.
He's brought honor to our family.
لقد جلب الشرف لعائلتنا.
What does a family of thugs even know about honor.
ماذا تعرف عائلة البلطجية عن الشرف؟
Finish up quickly and eat your meal.
انتهي بسرعة وتناول وجبتك.
Is something wrong?
هل هناك شيء خاطئ؟
You're in the papers.
أنت في الصحف.
What?
ماذا؟
SAVES THE COMMITTEE PRESIDENT FROM SUICIDE ATTEMPT
ينقذ رئيس اللجنة من محاولة انتحار
It means we've been blessed by our ancestors.
وهذا يعني أننا كنا محظوظين من قبل أسلافنا.
Yeah, right.
نعم، صحيح.
You getting a 15-year sentence and coming out in 10,
لقد حصلت على حكم بالسجن لمدة 15 عامًا وخرجت في 10،
now that is a blessing.
وهذا هو نعمة.
Come on, the day has barely even begun!
هيا، اليوم لم يبدأ بعد!
Stop annoying me.
توقف عن إزعاجي.
Then stop talking nonsense.
إذن توقف عن الكلام الهراء.
Does Seokcheol seem like he was born to be a thug?
هل يبدو أن سوكتشول قد ولد ليكون بلطجيًا؟
It's all because of your family.
كل هذا بفضل عائلتك.
Generations of thugs, starting with your father.
أجيال من البلطجية، بدءًا من والدك.
Will you stop it?
هل ستوقفها؟
My father wasn't any ordinary thug.
لم يكن والدي مجرد بلطجي عادي.
He fought the Japanese police during the Japanese invasion.
حارب الشرطة اليابانية أثناء الغزو الياباني.
He was a vigilante!
لقد كان حارسًا!
You make it sound like he was a freedom fighter.
لقد جعلته يبدو وكأنه كان مقاتلاً من أجل الحرية.
Jeez!
يا إلهي!
How dare they use my photo without permission--
كيف يجرؤون على استخدام صورتي دون إذن؟
What?
ماذا؟
Stop being reckless.
توقف عن التهور.
Why'd you run into a house when it was on fire?
لماذا ركضت إلى المنزل عندما كان يحترق؟
You're a thug, not a firefighter.
أنت بلطجي، وليس رجل إطفاء.
All right, I get it.
حسنا، فهمت ذلك.
Are you hurt anywhere?
هل أنت مصاب في أي مكان؟
I'm perfectly fine.
أنا بخير تماما.
Come on. Why didn't you just eat it?
هيا، لماذا لم تأكله فقط؟
Just eat what he gave you.
فقط أكل ما أعطاك إياه.
I don't want to indulge him.
لا أريد أن أستسلم له.
Here. You have it.
هنا. لديك ذلك.
- What are you doing? - Open up.
- ماذا تفعل؟ - افتح.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
I was just in the area.
لقد كنت للتو في المنطقة.
Thought I'd drop by and see how you were doing.
اعتقدت أنني سأمر وأرى كيف حالك.
Oh, uh...
أوه، اه...
Would you like this?
هل يعجبك هذا؟
Mmm.
ممم.
It's nice and sweet.
إنه لطيف وحلو.
You can have some later.
يمكنك الحصول على بعض منها لاحقًا.
The developers say they'll try and match your compensation request.
يقول المطورون أنهم سيحاولون مطابقة طلب التعويض الخاص بك.
Oh. Hey, kid.
أوه، يا صغيري.
My Miran said
قال ميران
I should thank you
ينبغي لي أن أشكرك
whenever I met you next.
عندما التقيت بك في المرة القادمة.
But I just can't...
ولكنني لا أستطيع...
get myself to say it, so just assume I did, and go away.
أجبر نفسي على قول ذلك، لذا افترض أنني قلت ذلك، ثم اذهب بعيدًا.
You're a better person than your father.
أنت شخص أفضل من والدك.
Well then, take care of yourself. Bye.
حسنًا، اعتني بنفسك. مع السلامة.
Wait.
انتظر.
You said you wanted to quit being a thug.
قلت أنك تريد التوقف عن كونك بلطجيًا.
Did you mean it?
هل قصدت ذلك؟
As someone who's been in your shoes, here's my advice:
كشخص كان في مكانك، إليك نصيحتي:
Brace yourself if you're going to quit.
استعد إذا كنت تنوي الاستقالة.
If not, you'll be stabbed in the back and abandoned by the ones you trust the most.
إذا لم تفعل ذلك، فسوف يتم طعنك في الظهر ويتم التخلي عنك من قبل الأشخاص الذين تثق بهم أكثر من غيرهم.
That's how it is.
هكذا هو الأمر.
Okay.
تمام.
What's the matter? Is it about Seokcheol not eating the meat you gave him?
ما الأمر؟ هل سوكتشول لم يأكل اللحم الذي أعطيته له؟
Tsk! What makes you say that?
تسك! ما الذي يجعلك تقول ذلك؟
His resentment won't fade so easily.
لن يتلاشى استياؤه بسهولة.
Remember when he was in elementary school?
هل تتذكر عندما كان في المدرسة الابتدائية؟
I remember.
انا أتذكر.
I remember it very vividly.
أتذكره بوضوح شديد.
Even at that age, he knew what you were thinking.
حتى في ذلك العمر، كان يعرف ما كنت تفكر فيه.
You went to your son's presentation as a father,
لقد ذهبت إلى عرض ابنك كأب،
but to him, you were a thug, not a father.
لكن بالنسبة له، كنت مجرد بلطجي، وليس أبًا.
And when you were in prison,
وعندما كنت في السجن،
you forced him to go to them and take their money.
أجبرته على الذهاب إليهم وأخذ أموالهم.
He hated it so much.
لقد كره ذلك كثيرًا.
Now he goes to the place he hates so much and calls it his workplace.
الآن يذهب إلى المكان الذي يكرهه كثيرًا ويسميه مكان عمله.
Oh, dear.
يا عزيزي.
As you know, when it came to demolition,
كما تعلمون، عندما يتعلق الأمر بالهدم،
we were always second to Kang Taehoon and his people.
لقد كنا دائمًا في المرتبة الثانية بعد كانغ تاي هون وشعبه.
But no matter what stunts they pull,
ولكن بغض النظر عن الأعمال المثيرة التي يقومون بها،
they can't do what Seokcheol did and risk their lives.
لا يمكنهم أن يفعلوا ما فعله سوكتشول ويخاطروا بحياتهم.
So, today's first toast
لذا، نخب اليوم الأول
is for Park Seokcheol and his brilliant work.
هذا من أجل بارك سوكتشول وعمله الرائع.
Everyone, cheers!
الجميع، هتاف!
Cheers!
هتافات!
Okay, everyone.
حسنا، الجميع.
The Chairman will now present the monetary reward!
وسوف يقدم الرئيس الآن المكافأة المالية!
- Thank you. - Good job.
- شكرا لك. - عمل جيد.
Congratulations!
مبروك!
Now, now!
الآن، الآن!
That's not all.
هذا ليس كل شئ
For our star of the day, Park Seokcheol,
لنجمنا اليوم، بارك سوكتشول،
the Chairman has prepared a special gift.
وقد أعد الرئيس هدية خاصة.
- Here. - Thank you.
- هنا. - شكرا لك.
Open it.
افتحه.
Try it on.
جربها.
- Thank you. - Applause!
- شكرا لك. - تصفيق!
Park Seokcheol!
بارك سوكتشول!
Park Seokcheol! Park Seokcheol!
بارك سوكتشول! بارك سوكتشول!
Those little shits.
تلك الأشياء الصغيرة.
Oseon E&C stabbed me in the back.
لقد طعنتني شركة Oseon E&C في ظهري.
With Changsoo, at that.
مع تشانغسو، في ذلك الوقت.
The headquarters ordered them to change the company.
أمرهم المقر بتغيير الشركة.
- Because of what Seokcheol did? - Yes.
- بسبب ما فعله سوكتشول؟ - نعم.
They changed their minds when they saw the news about District Three.
لقد غيروا رأيهم عندما رأوا الأخبار عن المنطقة الثالثة.
The jerk Kim Changsoo gets to hang in there thanks to Seokcheol.
يتمكن الأحمق كيم تشانغسو من التمسك بالسلطة هناك بفضل سوكتشول.
Sir, what will you do?
سيدي ماذا ستفعل؟
What else?
ماذا بعد؟
It's time for payback.
لقد حان وقت الانتقام.
Let's go, boss.
دعنا نذهب يا رئيس.
Jindeuk already gave him a heads-up, so don't worry.
لقد أعطاه جيندوك بالفعل إشعارًا مسبقًا، لذا لا تقلق.
GEUMMYEONG BANK
بنك جيوم يونغ
Shall we?
هلا فعلنا؟
Thank you for coming.
شكرا لحضورك.
We drink...
نحن نشرب...
- We drink instant. - Instant coffee, you mean?
- نشرب قهوة سريعة التحضير. - تقصد قهوة سريعة التحضير؟
- Get instant coffee. - Okay.
-احضر قهوة سريعة التحضير. -حسنا.
You're here to discuss the overdue loan at our branch, right?
أنت هنا لمناقشة القرض المتأخر في فرعنا، أليس كذلك؟
From what I know,
من ما أعرفه،
the loan is about 360 million won, and your house is collateral.
يبلغ القرض حوالي 360 مليون وون، ومنزلك هو الضمان.
- Yes, about that... - Yes.
- نعم، بخصوص ذلك... - نعم.
I'd like to extend the due date of the loan payment.
أرغب في تمديد تاريخ استحقاق سداد القرض.
Yes, of course.
نعم بالطبع.
CEO Lee Jindeuk is a long-term customer at our bank.
الرئيس التنفيذي لي جيندوك هو عميل طويل الأمد في بنكنا.
He called me and asked me to take good care of you.
لقد اتصل بي وطلب مني أن أعتني بك جيدًا.
Yes, I trust you'll handle it well.
نعم، أنا أثق بأنك ستتعامل مع الأمر جيدًا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
So, why don't we give it plenty of time and extend the period to, say, five years?
إذن، لماذا لا نعطيها الوقت الكافي ونمدد الفترة إلى خمس سنوات مثلا؟
Yes, well...
نعم حسنا...
That's good.
هذا جيد.
In that case, if you want an extension,
في هذه الحالة، إذا كنت تريد تمديدًا،
you'll need to pay back some of the principal.
سوف تحتاج إلى سداد جزء من رأس المال.
- Pay back some of the principal? - Yes.
- سداد جزء من رأس المال؟ - نعم.
Otherwise it's hard to get the HQ's screening department to approve it.
وإلا فمن الصعب الحصول على موافقة قسم الفحص في المقر الرئيسي.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
أعتقد أنه كان هناك سوء فهم.
I came to see you because I don't have that kind of money.
لقد جئت لرؤيتك لأنني لا أملك هذا النوع من المال.
Well, as I said just now,
حسنًا، كما قلت للتو،
you'll need to repay at least 70 million won.
سوف تحتاج إلى سداد ما لا يقل عن 70 مليون وون.
What? 70 million?
ماذا؟ 70 مليون؟
So, he needs to pay 70 million won just to get the deadline extended?
إذن فهو يحتاج إلى دفع 70 مليون وون فقط لتمديد الموعد النهائي؟
- Is that what you're saying? - Yes. That's exactly it.
- هل هذا ما تقوله؟ - نعم، هذا هو بالضبط.
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
Why didn't you just tell us about it at the beginning?
لماذا لم تخبرنا بذلك في البداية؟
Are you toying with us?
هل تلعب معنا؟
You're pissing me off!
أنت تغضبني!
Sir, you can't do this. Sir...
سيدي، لا يمكنك فعل هذا. سيدي...
- Listen up. - Yes.
-استمع. -نعم.
By when do I need to pay back the money?
متى يجب علي أن أسدد الأموال؟
What... In a week.
ماذا... في اسبوع.
I mean...
أعني...
In two weeks, yes. Two weeks.
في اسبوعين، نعم. اسبوعين.
- Two weeks? - Yes.
- اسبوعين؟ - نعم.
Do you know how unreasonable that is?
هل تعلم أن هذا غير معقول؟
Make it a month.
اجعلها شهرًا.
Sorry? One month...
عذرا؟ شهر واحد...
Okay. I'll try to make it a month.
حسنًا، سأحاول أن أجعله شهرًا.
I'll leave you to take care of the paperwork.
سأترك لك مهمة الاعتناء بالأوراق.
Okay.
تمام.
- It's hot! - Oh, no!
- إنه حار! - أوه، لا!
- Damn it. - I'm sorry.
- اللعنة. - أنا آسف.
- What's the matter with you people! - It's okay.
- ما الأمر معكم أيها الناس! - لا بأس.
It's fine. I can just wipe it off.
لا بأس، يمكنني مسحه.
- My goodness.
- يا إلهي.
Seriously.
بجد.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Jeez.
جيز.
That punk Jindeuk said it was all sorted.
قال ذلك الشاب جيندوك أن كل شيء تم حله.
This won't do. I'll give him an earful.
هذا لن ينفع، سأوبخه بشدة.
Don't call him.
لا تتصل به.
I'm sure he did his best.
أنا متأكد من أنه بذل قصارى جهده.
You're having to go through this all because of Seokkyung.
أنت مضطر إلى تحمل كل هذا بسبب Seokkyung.
By the way, will you be able to get that much money?
بالمناسبة، هل ستتمكن من الحصول على هذا القدر من المال؟
Boss.
رئيس.
- I'll sell my house. - You crazy...
- سأبيع منزلي. - أنت مجنون...
Don't be ridiculous.
لا تكن سخيفا.
At least let's go have some makgeolli.
على الأقل دعنا نذهب لتناول بعض الماكجولي.
Not today. I'm going home.
ليس اليوم. سأذهب إلى المنزل.
- Grandma, throw it! - Here.
- جدتي، ارميها! - هنا.
- Bounce. - My gosh.
- ارتداد. - يا إلهي.
I'm beat. Here.
أنا منهك هنا.
Can you go play on your own now? Throw it there.
هل يمكنك الذهاب واللعب بمفردك الآن؟ ألقِها هناك.
My goodness.
يا إلهي.
Gosh, good job.
يا إلهي، عمل جيد.
You're good at it.
أنت جيد في ذلك.
My gosh.
يا إلهي.
- Is it happening tomorrow? - Yes.
- هل سيحدث غداً؟ - نعم.
We'll meet tomorrow to get acquainted, fine-tune the details of the contract,
سنلتقي غدًا للتعارف وضبط تفاصيل العقد،
and bribe them a little.
وأرشوهم قليلا.
It'll all work out.
كل شيء سوف يعمل بشكل جيد.
Good to know.
من الجيد أن تعرف.
- Boss. - Yes?
- رئيس. - نعم؟
Like I said before, I'm leaving once this deal is settled.
كما قلت من قبل، سأغادر بمجرد تسوية هذه الصفقة.
You're ruining a perfectly good day again.
أنت تفسد يومًا جيدًا مرة أخرى.
Fine, you punk. I get it.
حسنًا، أيها الأحمق، فهمت.
Okay.
تمام.
Gosh, that punk.
يا إلهي، هذا الشرير.
- How are you doing nowadays? - It's tough.
- كيف حالك هذه الأيام؟ - إنه أمر صعب.
I need some results. I can't let them laze around.
أحتاج إلى بعض النتائج. لا أستطيع تركهم يتكاسلون.
Anything happening lately?
هل يحدث أي شيء في الآونة الأخيرة؟
Well...
حسنًا...
I think I can make something happen.
أعتقد أنني أستطيع أن أفعل شيئًا ما.
Would you like a present?
هل تريد هدية؟
I heard that Changsoo might be...
سمعت أن تشانغسو قد يكون...
It could work in our favor if you get the timing right.
قد يكون هذا لصالحنا إذا حصلت على التوقيت المناسب.
Goodness.
الخير.
This is why Changsoo can never beat you. You use your wits.
لهذا السبب لا يستطيع تشانغسو هزيمتك أبدًا. أنت تستخدم ذكائك.
It seems like you really hate Changsoo.
يبدو أنك تكره تشانغسو حقًا.
Not at all. I used to work for him.
لا على الإطلاق. كنت أعمل معه.
- Drink up. Let's get another round. - Okay.
- اشرب شوية. خلينا نروح نروح تاني. - تمام.
BAND AND SOLO AUDITION DARE TO BE A STAR
فرقة واختبار أداء فردي تجرؤ على أن تكون نجمًا
Go ahead first, sir. I'll catch up soon.
تفضل أولاً يا سيدي، سألتقي بك قريبًا.
- Escort him. - Yes, sir.
- رافقه. - نعم سيدي.
This way, sir.
من هنا سيدي.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Do you like music?
هل تحب الموسيقى؟
Oh, yes.
أوه نعم.
If you're here to watch the performance, it's downstairs.
إذا كنت هنا لمشاهدة العرض، فهو في الطابق السفلي.
Downstairs?
في الطابق السفلي؟
Oh, okay. Thank you.
حسنًا، شكرًا لك.
Welcome. Are you here alone?
مرحباً، هل أنت هنا وحدك؟
Oh, I want to sign up for the audition.
أوه، أريد الاشتراك في الاختبار.
You can do it online.
يمكنك القيام بذلك عبر الإنترنت.
I know, but I wanted to check out the vibe.
أعرف ذلك، ولكنني أردت التحقق من الأجواء.
Is it okay if I look around?
هل من المقبول أن أنظر حولي؟
Oh, okay, sure.
أوه، حسنًا، بالتأكيد.
- Go ahead. - Thank you.
- تفضل. - شكرا لك.
MYOUNGSAN INDUSTRIES
صناعات ميونغسان
That's spicy.
هذا حار.
- Is it good? - Yes.
- هل هو جيد؟ - نعم.
Yes.
نعم.
- Boss, do you have a minute? - No.
- يا رئيس، هل لديك دقيقة؟ - لا.
I just want to introduce some guys to you.
أريد فقط أن أقدم لكم بعض الرجال.
What?
ماذا؟
Come on in!
تفضل بالدخول!
Show him respect, boys. This is the famous Park Seokcheol.
أظهروا له الاحترام يا أولاد. هذا هو بارك سوكتشول الشهير.
Greetings, sir!
مرحباً سيدي!
- Who are they? - They're high-school bullies.
- من هم؟ - إنهم المتنمرين في المدرسة الثانوية.
Jeez.
جيز.
We've heard a lot about you, sir!
لقد سمعنا الكثير عنك يا سيدي!
Jang Wooseok of Myoungsan High School, 42nd batch.
جانج ووسوك من مدرسة ميونغسان الثانوية، الدفعة 42.
The schools around here come under my turf.
المدارس الموجودة هنا تقع تحت نطاق اختصاصي.
I aspire to be as cool as you someday.
أطمح أن أكون هادئًا مثلك يومًا ما.
Boys, come closer.
يا شباب، اقتربوا أكثر.
You know Mr. Kim Ku, right?
أنت تعرف السيد كيم كو، أليس كذلك؟
Kim...
كيم...
There's no teacher by that name in my school.
لا يوجد معلم بهذا الاسم في مدرستي.
He's not a schoolteacher.
إنه ليس معلمًا في المدرسة.
He fought for independence, against Japan.
ناضل من أجل الاستقلال ضد اليابان.
Gosh. I knew that.
يا إلهي، كنت أعرف ذلك.
- What? - I know Mr. Kim Ku.
- ماذا؟ - أعرف السيد كيم كو.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
There should be a book titled The Diary of Kim Ku in the library.
يجب أن يكون هناك كتاب بعنوان مذكرات كيم كو في المكتبة.
If you read the whole book and write a review,
إذا قرأت الكتاب كاملاً وكتبت مراجعة،
I'll accept you into the gang.
سأقبلك في العصابة.
Got it?
فهمتها؟
Yes, sir!
نعم سيدي!
Now, turn right.
الآن، اتجه إلى اليمين.
Now leave.
إذهب الآن.
Go on.
إستمر.
Do you think they'll read the book?
هل تعتقد أنهم سيقرأون الكتاب؟
Of course they won't.
بالطبع لن يفعلوا ذلك.
That's why I asked them to read it.
لهذا السبب طلبت منهم أن يقرؤوه.
- Did you read it? - Well...
- هل قرأته؟ - حسنًا...
The next time you bring kids like them to me, you're in serious trouble.
في المرة القادمة التي تحضر فيها أطفالًا مثلهم إليّ، ستكون في مشكلة خطيرة.
Okay, I'll try not to.
حسنًا، سأحاول عدم فعل ذلك.
- "Try not to"? - I won't bring them!
- "حاول ألا تفعل ذلك"؟ - لن أحضرهم!
Don't make me repeat myself.
لا تجعلني أكرر نفسي.
- Now leave me alone. - Yes, sir.
- الآن اتركني وحدي. - نعم سيدي.
Hello, sir!
أهلاً سيدي!
- Hi. - Guys, quick! Get up!
- أهلاً. - يا شباب، بسرعة! انهضوا!
Father.
أب.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I need to talk to Changsoo.
أريد أن أتحدث مع تشانغسو.
Talk about what?
تحدث عن ماذا؟
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Wait.
انتظر.
What do you mean, it's none of my business?
ماذا تقصد بأن هذا لا يعنيني؟
Look at your clothes...
أنظر إلى ملابسك...
You're not here to ask him for money, are you?
أنت لست هنا لطلب المال منه، أليس كذلك؟
Mind your own business. I'll handle it.
اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة، سأتولى الأمر.
It's my business, too.
إنه عملي أيضا.
Who do you think will have to pay back the money you borrow from him?
من تعتقد أنه سيتعين عليه سداد الأموال التي تقترضها منه؟
You know how hard I'll have to work to make up for it.
أنت تعرف مدى صعوبة العمل الذي سأضطر إلى القيام به للتعويض عن ذلك.
- You ungrateful-- - It's because of you...
- أنت جاحد-- - هذا بسببك...
that I got into this line of work.
أنني دخلت في هذا الخط من العمل.
- Oh, sir. You're here already? - Yes...
- يا سيدي، هل وصلتَ بالفعل؟ - نعم...
- Sorry I'm late. - That's okay.
- آسف على التأخير. - لا بأس.
Ah!
اه!
Seeing father and son together makes me feel so reassured.
رؤية الأب والابن معًا يجعلني أشعر بالاطمئنان.
- Shall we go in? - Sure.
- هل ندخل؟ - بالتأكيد.
This way, please.
من هنا من فضلك.
How is your father doing?
كيف حال والدك؟
PARK SEOKCHEOL
بارك سوكتشول
Where was he relocated to?
إلى أين تم نقله؟
Sangwol Prison, sir.
سجن سانجوول، سيدي.
Oh, dear. He keeps getting further away.
يا عزيزي، إنه يبتعد أكثر فأكثر.
I should visit him, but I just can't seem to make time for it.
ينبغي لي أن أزوره، لكن يبدو أنني لا أستطيع توفير الوقت لذلك.
Anyway...
على أي حال...
Here.
هنا.
Give this to your mother.
أعطي هذا لأمك.
- So, why did you want to see me? - Hmm.
- إذن لماذا أردت رؤيتي؟ - همم.
- How the business doing? All good? - Yes.
- كيف حال العمل؟ كل شيء على ما يرام؟ - نعم.
Thanks to Seokcheol, I can walk around with my head held high.
بفضل Seokcheol، أستطيع أن أتجول ورأسي مرفوع عالياً.
I'm so glad I took your advice back then.
أنا سعيد جدًا لأنني أخذت بنصيحتك في ذلك الوقت.
It's about my son.
إنه يتعلق بإبني.
Yes. Seokcheol?
نعم. سوكتشول؟
Give him a job at your company.
أعطيه وظيفة في شركتك.
The money you send to my house can be considered as his salary.
يمكن اعتبار الأموال التي ترسلها إلى منزلي بمثابة راتبه.
Does that work for you?
هل هذا يناسبك؟
You're Seokcheol, right?
أنت سوكتشول، أليس كذلك؟
In a way, you're part of our family, brat.
بطريقة ما، أنت جزء من عائلتنا، يا فتى.
Isn't that right?
أليس هذا صحيحا؟
I've heard you're a good fighter.
لقد سمعت أنك مقاتل جيد.
My God, look at that stare!
يا إلهي، أنظر إلى تلك النظرة!
He's ready.
إنه جاهز.
Whose fault is it...
من المخطئ؟
The Nice Guy
الرجل اللطيف
I didn't blindly get the money, don't worry.
لم أحصل على المال بشكل أعمى، لا تقلق.
You brat.
يا لك من شقي.
Just sit down with Seokcheol and tell him how you feel.
فقط اجلس مع Seokcheol وأخبره بما تشعر به.
I'd be a fool to expect him to understand me.
سأكون أحمقًا إذا توقعت منه أن يفهمني.
We have a problem!
لدينا مشكلة!
Some people are trying to take Go Jeongnim away!
يحاول بعض الناس أخذ جو جونغنيم بعيدًا!
Shouldn't we do something about Park Seokcheol too?
ألا ينبغي لنا أن نفعل شيئًا بشأن بارك سوكتشول أيضًا؟
Everything's set up.
تم إعداد كل شيء.
- Will you come see me tonight?
- هل ستأتي لرؤيتي الليلة؟
It's my first show.
هذا عرضي الأول.
Of course I will. I don't want to miss that.
بالتأكيد سأفعل. لا أريد أن أفوّت ذلك.
Boss, we got a problem.
يا رئيس، لدينا مشكلة.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
Beautiful.
جميلة.
It makes my heart ache.
إنه يجعل قلبي يؤلمني.